The Bellas were one big happy family. Then Renata met Sam...
Once Around is a comedy, drama, romance film directed by Lasse Hallström.
Renata Bella feels like a failure at life and career.
But when Renata attends a seminar on selling real
estate, she finally finds True Love.
Sam Sharpe, while a top-notch, successful salesman, is much older than Renata.
She is swept away by his excessively flamboyant style and irrepressible nature.
The very traits she finds romantic, however, lead to repeated conflict with her family,
especially her beloved father Joe, leaving Renata trapped in the middle.
Sam Sharpe, played by Richard Dreyfuss.
Renata Bella, played by Holly Hunter.
Joe Bella, played by Danny Aiello.
Jan Bella, played by Laura San Giacomo.
Marilyn Bella, played by Gena Rowlands.
Gail Bella, played by Roxanne Hart.
Once Around is a 1991 American romantic comedy-drama film about a young woman who falls for and eventually marries an overbearing older man
who proceeds to rub her close-knit family the wrong way, while exposing the dynamics of other family members along the way.
It stars Richard Dreyfuss, Holly Hunter, Danny Aiello, Laura San Giacomo and Gena Rowlands and was written by Malia
Scotch Marmo and directed by Swedish director Lasse Hallström, in his full English-language film debut.
The film explores themes of italian american, boston, massachusetts, romcom.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.